Kartik Bhaba

Contact no.: +1 (807) 355 4027 Email: Kartik.bhaba16@gmail.com Portfolio: https://kartikbhaba.vercel.app/ Github: https://github.com/KartikBhaba16

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kartik-bhaba-0251181b1

Profile

I am a senior at **Lakehead University**, **ON** currently pursuing **B. Sc Computers Science (Hons)**. I am an insightful person with strong core values who is passionate about learning and understanding computing technology. I have a reasonable experience in application development, IT and Sales. I'm a good percipient and I am a highly motivated and committed individual which makes me sincere, hardworking, and dependable. I have strong work ethics and am a sincere team player.

Work Experience

TELUS Wireless Consultant		Thunder Bay, ON 04/2024 - Present
 Created offerings for consumers demanding mobility, h 		
 Catered to a broader consumer segment with outbound 		
 Gained experience in offering a more diverse product re 	ange to clients.	
Staples Wireless Consultant		Thunder Bay, ON 09/2023 – 04/2024
 Contributed significantly towards increasing mobility s 	ervices and subscriptions.	
Dealt with diverse set of clienteles to cater to their mob	oility service needs.	
 Focused on cross selling efforts and mastering the skill with team synergistic alliances. 		
The Source (Bell) Electronics Inc. Sales Associate		Thunder Bay, ON 08/2022 - 04/2023
Catered to a diverse section of customers.		•
Created a complete solution for all customer needs.		
Worked in synergy with a diverse team to provide exce	ellent customer service.	
Unilink Global Consulting Co-founder		New Delhi, IND 09/2020 - 12/2020
• Successfully managed over 25 interns over the course of 3 months.		
· Created a complete website and managed social media		
Increased the reach of social media handles.	1	
Mobiquel Web-Development Intern		New Delhi, IND 07/2021 - 09/2021
Apprenticeship in web development technologies.		1.17 2000, 11.2 07/2021 07/2021
Created a chatbot program for the website of colleges a	ffiliated with Delhi University.	
Learned about workings of a tech company and deploy.		
Metvy.co Revenue Generation Intern		New Delhi, IND 04/2021 – 05/2021
• Assisted in revenue generation activities for venture expansion and business development.		110W Bellit, 111B 0 1/2021 03/2021
• Worked with core team and learnt about team building		
worked with cold team and learns accur team cantains	ee management	
Education		
Lakehead University B.Sc. Computer Science (Hons) Major GPA – 3.7 (4 th year) Algoma University B.Sc. Computer Science (Hons), 2nd Semester Springdales School, Pusa Road Senior School (XIIth Grade) Subjects: English, Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics and Computer Science Delhi Public School, Dwarka High School (Xth Grade)		Thunder Bay, ON 01/2022 - Present
		Brampton, ON 01/2021 – 01/2022
		New Delhi, IND 04/2019 – 08/2020
		New Delhi, IND 04/2017 – 05/2018
Skillset		
• C/C++	■ Git/GitHub	 Sales and marketing
- C/C++	- Gil/Gilnub	- Sales and marketing
Python, Pandas, NumPy, Scikit-learn	• AWS	 Team management
■ Tableau, Figma	 Java, JavaFX 	Problem-Solving
 Haxeflixel, Unity 	 Machine learning/ AI 	 Client Relations
 NextJS, React, Tailwind CSS 	 Financial Modeling, Analysis 	 Project-team management
 NextJS, React, Tailwind CSS 	• Financial Modeling, Analysis	 Project-team management

Projects

- 1) Machine learning based Automated driving system- Developed a machine learning based system as a group taking inputs from points and sensors deployed around subjects running tests. Developed in using Python libraries such as PyGame, Scikit-learn. Development lead to a steady increase in accuracy based on the machine learning models.
- 2) Automated chatbot processor using CSML Developed an automated chatbot system for online web deployment for a few universities under the esteemed Delhi University on behalf of Mobiquel. The chatbots are used to ease navigation through the website for prospective/existing students, using quick link directives on specific prompts.
- 3) Financial prediction of housing prices using Pandas and Machine learning- This program uses the power of machine learning to make accurate predictions on housing prices based on a set of features such as number of rooms, distance, landsize, building area, and year built.
- 4) Online telemedicine system for remote residents. A course project developed as a joint effort for the remote residents of Ontario seeking medical assistance, an online portal created and deployed where patients and caregivers can connect seamlessly.
- 5) Online sustainable clothing marketplace—Part of a hackathon project developed collectively for the devfest hackathon hosted by google, which comprised of an online frontend and a functional backend using technologies like Php and Sql to create and efficient marketplace for students to trade clothing and essential items using the on-campus distribution facilities.

Achievements

- 1) Dean's List Award Awarded for term year 2023-2024 at Lakehead University.
- 2) Second Position at DevFest Hackathon by Google Secured second position at the DevFest hackathon by contributing as a developer and designer to the sustainable clothing marketplace project.
- 3) President, Lakehead University Computer Science Club Selected as the president of the university computer science club for the year 2023-2024. Contributed to collaboration and partnership of the club with google to organize and host the Devfest Hackathon 2023 on campus.